求你了 不要
Please. Please don't.
天啊 不要
Please, god, no.
我讨厌这样 求你了
I hate this. Please!
欢迎回家 长毛
Welcome home, haircut.
图书馆还有更多的书
There's more at the library.
多得多
A lot more.
你们
You, uh…
你们有图书馆吗
You have a library?
你朋友达里尔
Your friend Daryl.
离开之前没机会看到
didn't get a chance to see it before he bounced.
他逃跑了吗
He escaped?
是的
Yeah.
你知道他在哪吗
You know where he is?
不知道
No.
如果我知道 我会告诉你的
I'd tell you if I did.
《旺达·N· 麦金太尔》
Vonda N. Mcintyre.
这本就行了
Th-this will be satisfactory.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
我给你弄点吃的 你想要什么
I'll get you something. What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I want?
是啊 吃什么 你想要什么
Yeah, to eat. What do you want?
什么都可以吗
Anything?
是啊 随便
Sure. Whatever.
真的吗 我想要什么都行
Really? Anything I want?
哥们 是的
Dude, yes.
想吃什么都行 你想吃什么
You can have anything. What do you want?
- 我能吃龙虾吗 - 不行
- Can I have lobster? - No, you can't have lobster.
你他妈以为这是什么地方
What the hell do you think this is?
有罐头意面和番茄酱吗
Do you have canned pasta and tomato sauce?
你想要橙色的还是红色的
You want orange-y or red?
橙色的
Orange-y.
好
All right.
有腌黄瓜吗 我爱吃腌黄瓜
What about pickles? I-I like pickles.
我们没腌黄瓜了
We're out of pickles.
那薯片呢
What about potato chips?
我们有薯片
We got chips.
42号做的
Number 42 makes them.
42号是这里人的代码系统吗
Number 42 is a coding system for persons here?
是工人的
For the workers, yeah.
他们做的是新鲜薯片吗
They make said chips fresh?
是啊 他们有个壶
Yeah, they got a kettle …
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
好 我十分钟后回来
Okay. I'll be back in 10.
享受你的新地方吧
Enjoy your new place.
（快走）
《行尸走肉》
早上好 小子
Good mornin', sunshine.
这和你回忆中的一样舒适吗
Is it just as cozy as you remember?
你跟你妻子和蒂娜去愚蠢的自驾游之后
You spent a lot of time on the wrong side of the door.
就花了许多时间待在门的错误一边
after that stupid road trip with the wife and Tina.
我们现在谈谈吧
So let's talk about now.
我们在边界周围花了几个小时
We went out looking for your little failed project.
寻找你的失败项目
for a few hours, just around the perimeter …
从头到尾找了一遍
Tip to taint, as it were …
就在我让人把你扔进这里的时候
right about the time I had you thrown in here,
我回来后
and when I got back,
意识到自己
I realized I…
少了个
was short…
妻子
a wife.
哪个
Which one?
雪莉
Sherry.
你知道些什么吗 小德
You know anything about that, Dwighty boy?
因为我得告诉你
'cause I got to tell you,
这真他妈太巧了
that is one hell of a coincidence,
达里尔走后几小时 她就离开了
her leaving just a few short hours after Daryl took off.
他根本没有靠武力打出去
Oh, and he didn't force his way out.
没有
No.
有人为他开门了
Somebody opened the door for him.
不是雪莉
It wasn't Sherry.
小德
Dwighty boy…
是你吗
Was it you?
事情往反方向发展了吗
Did it work the other way around?
你本该击溃他的
You were supposed to break him.
他把你感化了吗
Did he break you?
面对现实吧
I mean, let's face it …
你有一些合理的不满
You've got some pretty legitimate grievances.
你改变了对我的忠心吗 德怀特
You change your stripes on me, Dwighty?
你开始有不同的想法了吗
You startin' to see things different?
经历了这么多
After all this…
之前和之后
Before and after…
该死 经历了这么多之后
Hell, after everything…
你到底是谁 德怀特
…Who are you, Dwight?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
达里尔和你不一样
Daryl isn't like you.
他
He's…
有感情
Emotional.
所以他要么在回家的路上
So he's either on his way home,
要么在回这里的路上
Or he's coming back here.
试图多杀我们几个人
to try to kill some more of us.
主要是杀你和我
Mostly you and me.
无论怎样 我们都会找到他
Either way, we'll find him.
所以…
So…
你知道雪莉去了哪里吗
do you think you know where Sherry went?
知道
Yeah.
把她带回来
Bring her back.
解决这事
Sort it out.
给他缝缝针
Stitch him up.
把能治的地方都治一治
Fix what you can fix.
你不认为是她做的吗
You don't think she did it?
你觉得是她做的吗
You think she did?
我对她有些了解
I got to know her a little bit.
虽然不是很了解
Not well.
但足以想明白是怎么回事了
Well enough to know what happened.
她看见达里尔当时的处境
She saw Daryl in here, in the state he was in.
就把他放走了
She let him go.
她心软
She was soft.
很善良
She has a big heart.
你被打了一顿扔进牢里…
You were just beaten and thrown in a cell …
要我说的话很冤
unfairly, if you ask me.
现在你又重整旗鼓了
And you're back to it.
说不定你以后会为他掌管一个哨站
You may wind up running an outpost for him.
你懂的
You get it.
我觉得我也懂
I like to think that I do.
那种无私 温柔
The type of selfless, tender soul.
愿意嫁给尼根以救自己丈夫一命的人
who would marry Negan to save her husband's life?
也正是不应该…
That's exactly the kind of person who really isn't…
活到现在的人
expected to be around anymore.
谢了
Thanks.
只是想帮帮忙而已
Just trying to help.
这里有大家种植的 制造的
Stuff people grow, stuff people make,
以及搜刮的东西
stuff, you know, people scavenge.
啤酒 面包 剪头
Beer, bread, cut your head.
剪什么
Cut your what?
理发师
Barber.
也许能拯救一下你头上那坨东西
Might be able to kill that thing on your head.
我们用的是工分系统
We use a points system.
你现在是我们中的一员了 和他们不一样
You're one of us now, not them.
他们伙食糟糕 我们吃香喝辣
They eat shit, we eat good.
写下你拿了什么 或者让他们做了什么
Write what you took or what they did,
然后写上对应的点数 再签个名
how much it was worth, sign your name.
就这么简单
That's it.
今天一定是你的幸运日 长毛
Must be your lucky day, haircut.
这些是自家做的吗
Are these homemade?
是的
Yeah.
真是不错的手工腌菜
That's some good DIY stuff there.
不…不用了 谢谢
No … no, thank you.
你想要什么
You want something…
就拿什么 长毛
you take it, haircut.
我们让西蒙过去看一眼
We'll send Simon over to take a peak,
先来软的
sort of good-cop this thing first,
看看有什么效果
see how far we get.
他来了
There he is.
全场焦点
Man of the hour!
过来 大块头
Come on over here, big fella.
别这么没礼貌 混蛋
Don't be rude, asshole.
说「你好」啊
Say hello.
你…好
H-h-hello.
你有名字吗 混蛋
You got a name, asshole?
尤金
Eugene.
轮到我们了
Now us.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
尤金…
Well, Eugene…
我知道你还记得露西尔
I know you remember Lucille.
你看见这里这个东西了吗
Now, you see this right here?
你可能得靠近点仔细看看
You might have to get real close.
我的朋友 那是你造的子弹
That, my friend, is the bullet you made.
在正常情况下
Now, under normal circumstances,
我会一遍又一遍地让你亲密接触它
I'd be showing you that real close over and over again.
但是 尤金 你瞧
But, Eugene, see,
我只想知道你是不是个机灵鬼
all I really want to know is if you are a smarty-pants.
你懂的很多吗
You know things?
回答我
Answer the question.
我…我确实挺机灵的
I … I am, indeed, a smarty-pants.
我…自学了造子弹
I…taught myself to cast bullets.
我…找到了一个…
I…found a …
找到了一个机械车间
found a machine shop.
那里有必需的…
with the necessary…
我读了很多书…
I-I read a lot, and, um…
尽管我…
although my …
尽管我做不到过目不忘
Even though my memory is not considered eidetic,
但我也不会走马观花
I don't skim and I don't scrimp.
假如书上有什么知识
If knowledge is dropped,
我确实会学会
I do, indeed, pick it up.
你真的只是个混蛋而已
Oh, you really are just some asshole.
不 我不是
N-no. I'm not.
我有好几个生物化学
I have PHDs in biochemistry,
还有免疫学与微生物学博士学位
as well as immunology and microbiology,
我完成了博士学位 所以是货真价实的博士
and I've completed my doctorate, which makes me a doctor.
灾变之前
Prior to the collapse,
我是人类基因组计划十人小组的成员
I was part of a 10-person team at the human genome project,
受布鲁克斯·埃利斯博士领导
working under Dr. T. Brooks Ellis.
研制对抗病毒武器的病毒武器
to weaponize diseases to fight weaponized diseases.
以毒…攻毒
Fire with, uh… You know…fire.
不同部门间喝过酒…
Well, see, interdepartmental drinks were …
好吧 机灵鬼博士
All right, Dr. Smarty-pants.
你应该能不费吹灰之力解决这事
You ought to be able to crack this without breaking a sweat.
你看 围栏边我有很多免费劳工
You see, I have a lot of free labor here at the fence,
活死人可以防止其他杂碎进来
living dead pricks that help keep the riffraff out.
问题是它们站不住 总是会散架
Problem is, they don't keep. They fall apart.
就像那摊可怜的
Like that poor sack of…
狗屎玩意
pile of shit there.
所以 机灵鬼博士
So, Dr. Smarty-Pants,
怎么才能让他们站住
How do we keep them on their feet?
你们
You, um…
经常冶炼 对吗
smelt on the regs, correct?
我看到一堆遗留设备当中
I saw that among the legacy equipment on the floor that.
- 有可运作的熔炉 - 是又怎么样
- you possess an operational smelter. - And?
你已经掌握了解决问题的办法
You already possess the means to resolve your issue.
第一步 熔化金属废料
Step one, melt down scrap metal.
第二步 铁链拴住行尸
Step two, pour it over the compromised walker.
把金属液浇到它们身上
as they are in contact with the chain link.
液态金属会变硬
The liquid metal will harden…
既可以保持行尸身体完整
Both maintaining bodily integrity for the walker.
又可以把它们粘在围栏上
as well as affixing them to the fence.
更棒的是遮盖了它们的头部
Bonus points for covering their head.
防止敌人攻击或意外发生导致脑袋碎裂
and protecting them from head trauma from hostiles and calamities.
我靠
God damn!
这是我这辈子听过的最酷的主意
If that ain't the coolest thing I've ever heard in my life!
不但可行 而且霸气
Not only is that practical, it is just bad-ass!
看看你 机灵鬼博士
Look at you, Dr. Smarty-pants.
瑞克有没有让你替他做这些有意义的事
Did Rick have you doing this kind of valuable stuff for him?
他亏了 我们赚了
His loss, our gain.
我觉得应该给你签约奖金
I feel like I need to give you some kind of signing bonus here.
我已经得到了腌黄瓜
Uh, w-well, I wa… I was gifted these pickles.
不
No.
作为对你的答谢
As a token of my gratitude,
我要送我的老婆们
I'm gonna send you over a few of my wives.
到你房间去 让你乐一乐
to your apartment tonight, show you a good time.
现在我不用担心这事了
Now, I don't think I have to worry about this.
但谁又知道你到底有多聪明呢
But who knows how truly smart you are?
不准上床
No sex.
那是禁区
That is a grave no-no.
但你可以吃顿惬意的晚餐
However, you can have a little dinner,
喝喝小酒 乐呵乐呵
some drinks, share a few laughs.
没什么比漂亮妞的体香
There is nothing like beautiful women that smell good.
更让你觉得自己又像个人类了
to make you feel human again.
这方面我完全不了解
I wouldn't know anything about that.
你刚才说「老婆们」 是指有很多吗
D-d-did you say "Wives", meaning plural?
正是
Hell yes, I did.
机灵鬼博士要对
What does Dr. Smarty-pants say.
他在世界上最好的新朋友说什么吗
to his new bestest friend in the whole wide world?
要说什么吗
What does he say?
谢谢
Thank you.
非常地 完全地
Fully, completely…
诚心地 认真地感谢你
Sincerely, seriously…Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
去找点乐子吧
Why don't you go have some fun?
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell am I even looking at?
类似小虫子的生物叫亚尔
The insect-like creature is called Yar.
它们试图报复
It is attempting to exact revenge.
恶魔昆塔 因为它摧毁了拉扎克四
upon the evil Qotile for the destruction of Razak IV.
也许你该放松点 安珀
Maybe you should take it easy, Amber.
也许我不应该 弗兰基
Maybe I shouldn't, Frankie.
我们可以玩点别的
Uh, we could play something else.
战神
Warlords?
可以四个人玩 很有趣
It's four-player and quite the hoot.
你想玩什么都行
Whatever you want.
今晚为你服务
This is your night.
想来个按摩吗
Do you want a massage?
尼根很喜欢
Negan loves them.
我是认证按摩师
And I was a licensed therapist.
以前是
You know, before.
感谢你的好意
While I appreciate the gesture.
还有你对分配对象的认真精神
and your commitment to your assigned objective,
我非常清楚今晚你们没有一位是
I am fully aware that none of you ladies are here this evening.
出于自愿来的
of your own volition.
电子游戏是我唯一可以展示给你们的乐子
Video games are all about me showing all of you a fun time.
还想再吃点微波炉爆米花吗
Would you care for more microwave popcorn?
虽然这是尼根的主意
Hey, just because this was Negan's idea.
但不意味着我们不愿意来
doesn't mean that we don't want to be here.
只要有理性谈话 我就愿意来
I'd be down with just having an intelligent conversation.
我想在目前的情况下
Well, I suppose a conversation would be acceptable.
谈话是可以接受的
under the current circumstance.
你们想谈什么
What would you like to talk about?
人类基因组计划怎么样
Uh, how about the human genome project?
我可以聊一整晚这玩意
I could talk about that shit all night.
说实话
In truth…
我在人类基因组计划中的主要工作
The bulk of my work for the HGP.
属于黑盒子项目的一部分
fell under the auspices of the black box program,
而我无权谈论此事
of which I am not at liberty to discuss.
就算我可以
In all likelihood, even if I could,
你们也很可能无法理解
it'd probably escape your comprehension.
他刚侮辱了我们吗 塔尼娅
Did he just insult us, Tanya?
这不是侮辱
It was not a dis.
仅仅是陈述事实
It was simply a statement of fact.
我的智商经历了客观测量
My intelligence has been objectively measured.
我是个鹤立鸡群的人
I am fully a man apart.
那你就是那种
So, what, are you, like, one of those guys.
能用漂白剂
who can make a bomb.
和牙签什么的做炸弹的人咯
out of bleach and a toothpick or something?
当然不是
Of course not.
那至少需要干酵母 过氧化氢
That would at least require dry yeast, hydrogen peroxide,
少量洗洁精
and a small amount of liquid dish soap,
也许还要一些洁厕灵或者通渠剂
maybe some, you know, bathroom or drain cleaner,
一些气球之类的
some balloons or something like that,
再加一些常见的生活用品
few other common household sundries.
真的吗
Seriously?
千真万确
Serious as sepsis.
真的吗
Seriously?
真蠢
So stupid.
我希望这能表现我的聪明
I'm hoping to illustrate the opposite.
只是奴隶吗
Just slaves?
你说什么
Excuse me?
随便了
Whatever.
尤金博士 你刚用厕所里的东西制造了氦气吗
Dr. Eugene, did you just make helium out of toilet stuff?
是氢气
Hydrogen.
没事 基诺
It's cool, Keno.
我们没事
We're good.
放松
Relax.
你是我们中的一员了
You're one of us.
我应该提前说明
I should disclose in advance.
我将其归类为炸弹也许是有点说大话
I may have oversold this one by classifying it as a bomb.
过氧化氢分解时
As the hydrogen peroxide decomposes,
这一反应会以放热的形式释放能量
the reaction will release energy in the form of heat.
尤金博士 你能给我们看点精彩的吗
Dr. Eugene, can you please just show us some good shit?
我要点燃这根蜡烛
I'm gonna light this candle.
- 真酷 - 终于
- Cool! - Finally.
不 我是说 我要点燃这根蜡烛
No, I mean, I'm gonna light this candle.
不
Oh, no.
耶
Yay!
好棒
Yeah!
亲爱的
Honey?
D 我们总是说如果我们分开了
D … we always said that if we got separated,
我应该回到这里等你
I should come back here and wait for you.
你会带着啤酒和椒盐脆饼出现
You'd show up with beer and pretzels.
你记得吗
You remember that?
我知道
I know.
你也许不记得了
You probably don't.
你总说我们开始约会时
You always said that when we started dating,
你忘记告诉我你记性很差了
you forgot to tell me you had a shitty memory.
你以前会因此很沮丧
You used to get so frustrated by it…
知道你不会记得那些好时光
knowing you wouldn't remember those good days…
特别的日子
those special days.
（喂金鱼 爱你的雪莉 快走）
我为你感到难过
I felt bad for you.
我记得你说过
I remember you said.
你有许多想记住的事
there was so much you wanted to hold on to,
但你就这样忘了
and then it'd be gone.
但你很幸运你记性不好 D
But you're lucky you don't remember things, D.
真希望我现在能等你
I wish I could wait for you now.
但我不知道你会跟我走
But I don't know if you'd come with me.
还是带我回去
Or if you'd take me back there.
还是杀了我
Or you'd kill me.
你不想活在那个世界里
You didn't want to live in that world,
是我逼你的
and I made you.
我那样做是因为我不想让你死
I did what I did because I didn't want you to die.
但现在你杀人了
But now you've killed,
成为了你不想成为的人
and you've become everything you didn't want to be,
这是我的错
And it's my fault.
你比我更好
You were better than me.
大部分人都是
Most people are.
我放达里尔走
I let Daryl go.
因为他让你想起了以前的自己
Because he reminded you of who you used to be.
而我想让你忘掉
And I wanted to let you forget.
我不觉得自己能在外面活下去
I don't think I'm gonna make it out here,
但你错了
but you're wrong.
在那里并不比死了更好
Being there isn't better than being dead.
而是更糟
It's worse.
我希望你能明白
I hope you realize that,
希望你能离开那
and I hope you get away.
我希望你记得那些美好的时光
I hope you remember the good days,
哪怕只记得一点 但是…
even just one of them, but…
我不认为你会想起来
I don't think you will.
你也许根本不会读到这封信
I don't think you'll ever read this.
我爱以前的你
I loved who you were.
很抱歉 我让你变成了现在这样
I'm sorry I made you into who you are.
再见
Goodbye.
亲爱的
Honey.
我们听到你在玩亚尔和昆塔了 尤金
We can hear the Yars and the Qotile, Eugene.
在我的理解里 昨晚的事情
I was given to understand that last night's shinny.
应该是单一偶发事件
was supposed to be a singular incident.
不是他叫我们来的
He didn't send us.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
昨晚你看到安珀的样子了
You saw Amber last night.
喝了哭 哭了喝
She just drinks and cries.
她不想做这个
She didn't want this.
我们是自愿的
We signed up for it.
对我们来说更好
It's better for us.
她是被迫的
She had to.
她妈妈需要药
Her mom needed meds.
她又不能干活
She can't work.
安珀本以为
Amber thought…
她可以忍受
that she could live with it.
她做不到
She can't.
她求我们帮她结束这一切
She asked us to help her end it.
你们没有可做的
You aren't afforded any…
心理健康辅导吗
mental-health services?
没有
No.
- 你是认真的吗 - 你们有认证女按摩师
- Are you serious? - I mean, there's a licensed masseuse here.
按概率来说 应该…
Uh, odds being what they are …
没有那样的人
There's no one like that here.
只能这样了
So this…is it.
她只是想吃点什么
She just wants to take something.
睡过去 再不醒过来
She wants to go to sleep and not wake up.
那样非常不负责任
That would be wildly irresponsible.
她在睡梦中死去
She dies at night, in her sleep,
变成行尸的时候 其他人都在睡觉
she turns while everyone is asleep…
我们负责处理那部分
We'll handle that part.
我们希望你能帮她做点什么
We were hoping that you could make something for her,
因为我们知道你会做东西
'cause we know that you can make things.
我知道这很疯狂 你也不怎么了解我们
Look, I know that this is crazy and you barely know us…
但是我们知道你是个好人
But we can tell that you are a good man.
现在好人不多了
There aren't many of those left.
事实上 我不是好人
Truth of the matter is, I'm not good.
我不守序 不中立 不叛逆
I'm not lawful, neutral, or chaotic …
以上都不是
None of the above.
你是说你做不了是吗
Are you saying you can't do it?
并不是能力缺失的问题
Lack of ability is not the problem here.
我可以用现有的材料
I could jerry-rig a lethal toxin.
随意提取出某种致命毒素
with the assets at hand here.
- 没问题 我是… - 那就帮帮我们
- No problemo. I have the … - Then help us.
一片药 一小杯药水 都可以
A pill, a shot, whatever.
我们需要两份
We need two of them.
因为我们不知道什么时候才有机会
'cause we don't know when we could get our chance.
无论我们帮不帮她 她都要寻死的
She's gonna do it, with or without us.
她会很痛苦 或者导致其他人受伤
She'll suffer, and maybe someone else will get hurt.
你是好人 尤金
You are good, Eugene.
你一定要是
You have to be.
她有多重
How much does she weigh?
不知道 一百二吧
Don't know. Maybe…120.
怎么了
Why?
如果你们能告诉我她的准确体重
If you could get me her exact weight,
我可以保证做出半精加工无痛毒药
I could guarantee a semi-precise t.O. Pain-free d.
尽快做出
A.S.A.P.
目前只能这样了
Best I can do for now.
晚点再来吧
Come back later.
我们几个人玩扑克
We're playing poker with some guys.
试着帮你牵线
Try to hook you up.
你在开玩笑吗 玩不了扑克了
You kidding? Can't play poker.
明天早上天一亮
I got to be out diggin' postholes.
我就得出去挖坑
at the crack of dawn tomorrow.
我需要一板铝塑包装的
I would like a single blister pack.
最强效的感冒胶囊
of your most extra-strength cold capsule.
队是用来排的
The line's a line!
怎么 你老家都不排队吗
What, they not have them where you come from?
你不知道怎么排吗
You don't know how they work?
不 我熟悉…
No, I am familiar …
后面排着去 混蛋
Get in it, prick.
你的编号是多少
What is your number?
你的呢
What's yours?
16.
好吧 16号
All right, number 16.
我是尤金·波特博士
My name is Dr. Eugene Porter.
我最近被赋予了
I've recently been appointed.
这里新设立的首席工程师之职
to the newly created post of chief engineer of this facility.
我直属尼根管理
I report directly to Negan,
这意味着你直属我管理
which means you report directly to my ass.
我要感冒胶囊 快点
The cold capsules, now.
我不知道
I didn't know.
只是 来的新人很多…
We just … we get so many new faces, I didn't…
这个我也要
I want this, too.
还有这个
And this.
我不知道你管这叫什么
I don't even know what you call this.
我要叫它小黏糊
I'm gonna call it a gremblygunk.
你找到她了吗
Did you find her?
她在哪
Where is she?
我杀了她
I killed her.
她逃向了一群行尸中
She ran away from me right into a mess of dead ones,
所以我…给了她痛快
So, I, uh… Made it quick.
还是会痛
It still hurts.
有绷带好一些
Feels better with a bandage.
我不是说这个
I wasn't talking about that.
我本想告诉你忘了她 但是…
I would tell you to just forget about her, but…
考虑到她做的事情 我不觉得短时间内
…I don't see anyone else doing that anytime soon,
会有人这么做
considering what she did.
我们都做过一些事情
Oh, we've all done things.
是的 但在我们来这里之前
Yes, but before we got here,
在我们懂得之前
Before we understood…
我们像个懦夫
We were cowards about it.
我们…不能留有善良之心
We don't … we don't get to have big hearts.
记住这一点
Remember that.
这是干什么
Wh-what is this?
你会知道的
You'll find out.
你最好睁眼好好看着
You are gonna want to pay close attention to this.
不
no, no, no, no!
为什么
Why?
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
我发现这个小纪念品
I found this little souvenir.
藏在你的桌子里
tucked away in your desk.
我不知道那是什么
I-I-I don't know what that is.
你
You…
开门放走了我的宠物
left the door open and let my puppy out.
你知道雪莉不喜欢达里尔在这里
You knew Sherry hated Daryl being here,
所以你为她放了他 趁机逞英雄
So you let him out for her, be the hero.
然后你就可以插一脚了
Then you could move in.
你…
That…
真够狡猾
is some weaselly shit right there.
我没这么做 是她自己逃跑的…
But I didn't. She's the one who ran …
她逃跑
Oh, she ran?
你知道为什么她会逃吗
You know why she ran?!
因为她知道我会怪她
Because she knew I would blame her, which…
确实如此
I did.
但是雪莉在她被撕碎之前
But, see, Sherry told Dwighty boy the whole story.
告诉了小德整件事的经过
right before she was torn apart.
一个超级辣妹 因为你的
A super hot girl, horrifically killed.
痴心妄想和小鸡鸡
Because of your greedy, delusional,
被残忍杀死
and tiny little prick.
这不是真的 德怀特
It's not true. Dwight?
他在撒谎
He's lying about it.
- 我决不会这么做 - 为什么
- I would never do that. - Why?
为什么 为什么他要撒谎呢
Why? Why would he do that?
为什么他要故意伤害你呢
Why would he intentionally try to hurt you?
雪莉死了
Sherry's gone.
如果他撒了谎
And if he's lying…
她还活着 我会找到她
And she's out there, I will find her.
然后我会烧了他另外半张脸
And then I will burn the other side of his face off.
直到他死
until he dies.
他能从中得到什么好处呢
So, what was he gonna get out of this?
不
No.
我了解我的小德
You see, I know my Dwighty boy.
他需要的只是
See, all he needed…
在牢房里再被关一晚
was one more night in the hole,
然后脑子就正常了
get his head screwed on straight.
以前管用 现在也管用
It worked before, and it worked now.
是不是啊 德怀特
Ain't that right, Dwight?
是的
Oh, yeah.
求求你
oh, please.
不 求求你
No, please.
求求你
Please, please, please!
天啊 不要烫我
Oh, jesus, don't burn me.
求求你
Please!
不
No.
不 求求你
No, no, please!
你知道我讨厌这样做
Now you know I hate this shit.
只用告诉我是你做的 你很抱歉
Just tell me you did it and that you're sorry,
我就不用动手了
And I don't have to do this.
是的
Yes.
是我做的 都是我做的
Yes, I did it … all of it.
抱歉 我很抱歉
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
求求你
Please…
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这么说就行了
That's all you had to say.
That is all you had to say.
幸好我们还有个卡森医生
A good thing we got a spare Dr. Carson.
我相信你 小德
I trust you, Dwighty boy.
从来不该怀疑你
Never shoulda doubted you.
雪莉是我最喜欢的女人之一
Sherry was one of my favorites.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我不
I'm not.
冷血
Ice-cold.
我喜欢
I love it.
进
Come.
你好
Hello.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
挺好的
Better than that.
你可以下局玩 不过要等一会
You can call next, but it might be a while.
你做药了吗
Did you make the pills?
做了
I did.
但不能给你们
But you can't have them.
安珀指望着我们呢
Amber's counting on us.
我们跟她说你会帮助我们
We told her that you were gonna help us,
- 她说她… - 住嘴 红发
- and she says that she … - Pump your brakes, red.
别侮辱我的智商 弗兰基
Do not insult my intelligence, Frankie.
药不是给安珀的
Said pills aren't for Amber.
药是给尼根的
Said pills are for Negan.
所以你要两份
That's why you wanted two.
他不是杀了你的朋友们吗
Didn't he kill your friends?
杀了好几个
Several.
但我们也杀了他的三十多个人
But I imagine we killed about 30 or so of his.
扯平了
Turnabout and all that.
给我们药 不然我们向尼根告状
Give us the pills, or we'll tell Negan about it.
我们会说做药是你的主意
We'll tell him that it was your idea to make them.
你试图劝我们协助你
and that you tried to get us to help.
那会是你的战术错误
That would be a tactical error on your part.
他会信我而不是你
They'll believe me over you.
正如他信德怀特而不是医生一样
for the same reason he believed Dwight over the doctor.
你对他来说是可取代的
You're replaceable to him.
另一方面 我则不是
I, on the other hand, am not.
你是个懦夫
You're a coward.
你是个…懦夫
You're…a coward.
这是正确的评价
That is a correct assessment.
我能进来吗
May I come in?
你喜欢这里吗
So, how you liking it here?
我们把机灵鬼博士招待得好吗
Are we doing right by Dr. Smarty-pants?
弗兰基和塔尼娅
You know, Frankie and Tanya…
她们说的都是你的好话
Nothing but good things to say about you.
没关系
It's all right.
我明白
I get it.
我知道接受改变
I know how hard it can be to accept change,
弃暗投明有多难
to get on the right team.
但是我需要你明白一些事
But I need you to understand something.
我不会随意邀请他人
I do not make this invitation to everyone.
我的邀请分量也很重
And I sure as shit do not make it lightly.
你不用再害怕了
You do not need to be scared anymore.
你不用害怕了
You don't need to be scared.
只用回答我一个问题
You just have to answer me one question.
这是个大问题
And it's a big one.
你是…
Who are …
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
我完完全全 彻头彻尾是尼根
I'm utterly, completely, stone-cold Negan.
遇见你之前我就是尼根了
I was Negan before I even met you.
遇见你之后 我才醒悟
I just needed to meet you properly to know.
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
当心点
Hey, be careful with that.
你想被熔态金属烫到吗
Hey, you want to get burned by molten metal?
因为那样做会被熔态金属烫到的
'cause that's exactly how you get burned by molten metal.
关于我施压…
Regarding me clamping down …
你跟我们一伙吗
You on board?
是的 和你一样
I am. Just like you.
- 不知道你是否记得我名字 - 不记得
Don't know if you recall my handle … I don't.
尤金
Eugene.
你是德怀特
You're Dwight.
我们都是尼根
We are Negan.
是啊
Yeah.